# HASSAN ALASMARI

INTERNAL COMMUNICATION SPECIALIST, PR, CONTENT CREATOR



#### CONTACTS

+966541000557 hassanyahay1987@gmail.com Saudi Arabia, Riyadh

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor Media and** Communication, Umm Al-Qura University, Makkah 2014

Average: 3.12\4

**High Diploma Business** and Comprehensive Project Management, Asia e University Malaysia, Malaysia Kuala Lumpur 2019

Intensive English course, California Language Center - Malaysia , Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia 2019

#### SKILLS

MS Office

Creative writing

Media management

Social media management

leadership communication

Project management

Blogger management

Public Relations and Protocol

Customer Service and

Tourism planning

Team Work and Communication

Authorization, guidance and management

Email marketing

Digital Marketing

## LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

#### ABOUT ME

A Saudi national that has a passion for media, Strong corporate communications professional, experience in media and PR and Hotel operations management with 8 vears expertise.

I have a desire to discover myself with a creative team capable of change and achievement.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Internal Communication Specialist, content writer, at Family affairs council, Riyadh

Sep 2022 - Present

Social Media Content Creator, at Rayz creative digital agency, Riyadh Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

Social Media Content Creator, at KSA Pavilion EXPO 2020 Dubai, United Arab **Emirates Dubai** 

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022

Content Writer, Bassmat | Integrated Agency, Riyadh

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

Remote work Commissioning to move to Dubai to manage the Expo

Hotel Operations Supervisor at Crown Rose, The Legacy Rose & Crown Hotel, Riyadh

Nov 2020 - Aug 2021

Guest Service Supervisor - Centro Waha Riyadh by Rotana, Rotana Hotel Management Corporation PJSC, Riyadh

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

Night Manager Almarwa Rayhaan by Rotana, Rotana Hotel Management Corporation PJSC, MAKKAH

Mar 2014 - Mar 2019

Conference coordinator and photographer, The Institute of Hajj and Umrah Research, Makkah

May 2013 - Sep 2013

Graduation project

News and Reports Editor, University newspaper and electronic newspapers, Makkah

Jan 2011 - Feb 2012

Blogger, Hassan's blog, Makkah

Feb 2009 - Present

website & Portfolio

https://sites.google.com/view/hassaalasmari

## COURSES

Crisis Leadership, Deakin University

Apr 2023

Intercultural Communication, Shanghai International Studies University

Apr 2023

Fundamentals of project management, Google

Mar 2023

Introdution to Digital Journalism, Reuters

Mar 2023

Organizing press conferences, Institute of Public Administration-Saudi Arabia

Apr 2020

Preparing media campaigns, Institute of Public Administration-Saudi Arabia Apr 2020

Effective Online Presence, Aljazeera

Effective interview Planning, Aljazeera

The Fundamentals of Event Management, Doroob Feb 2020

Internatioal Computer Driving License, Edraak Apr 2019

**Principles of Customer Service, Doroob** Jul 2018

Public speaking skills, Edraak Jul 2017

## AWARDS AND HONORS

Achieving the second place in the high school diploma in 2009.

6 letters of thanks from the General Manager for the excellent performance and improvement of the guests experience.

Certificate of growth and achievement of sales.

# HOBBIES

Research, Monitor Social Media, Travel, Documentaries